CONTACT ME AT

Dziyura.com

dziyura@gmail.com

(310)880-42-43

in @dziyura

SKILLS SUMMARY

- Product Management
- Product Launch, Product Design
- Leadership, Management
- Iira
- Launching/Developing MVP
- Design
- Analytical
- · Presentation
- Business Applications
- Confluence
- Organizational Skills
- · Lead Generation
- Attention To Detail
- Time Management
- Problem-Solving
- CRM
- SEM and SEO Marketing
- Agile,SCRUM

TECH KNOWLEDGE

• Programming languages:

HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, Python

• Dev tools:

React, NodeJS.

• Database:

MySQL, MongoDB

• Cloud:

AWS, Azure

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Moscow State Institute Of International Relations

Bachelor's Degree, International Jurisprudence | Sep 2009 - Jul 2013

YURA DZHISHKARIANI

PERSONAL PROFILE

Diligent Product Manager offering years of industry success, including product roadmap development, building features from scratch, market research and data analytics. Highly skilled in identifying opportunities to maximize revenue. Driven and strategic with a proven history of superior market penetration and product launch abilities with high-touch design.

Work Experience

Customer Success Manager

Phonexa | 01/2021 -05/2021

Glendale, CA

- Worked closely with Product Managers and Software Developers developing a new set of features leading to improvement of customer satisfaction rate and platform usage by 30%.
- Led over 17 projects implementing SaaS and client-server implementation projects at 2 remote locations (USA and UK).
- Collaborate with clients to recommend new business opportunities (website options, API integration, white labeling, etc) and strategies to increase the volume of business.
- Led creation and training for overseas 24/7 customer support team of 9 people.
- Created and updated Knowledge Base articles to improve "adoption".
- Worked closely with the design and the product team on developing UI/UX improvements based on collected feedback.

Co-Founder - Product Manager

Naks | 01/2019 - 01/2021

Los Angeles, CA

- Defined product features, roadmap, and a financial plan. Negotiated and managed vendor relationships, managed an engineering team to successfully launch products and generated \$100k+ in revenue in the first year.
- Collaborated and improved customer checkout process which led to a 15% increase in conversion rate and 25% engagement rate.
- Increased sales by 30% by implementing a new sales strategy and original email marketing campaign.
- Increased sales by 15% by determining needs, delivering solutions, and overcoming objections through skills in identifying customer pain points.
- increased retention rate by 40% by Investigating and solving customers' problems regarding products, prices, and availability to maintain long-lasting relationships.
- Developed and launched paid marketing campaigns (Google ads, Facebook ads, Pinterest ads, and Linkedin ads).

Account Manager

Don-Stroy Invest | Jun 2015 - Nov 2018

- Overhauled client onboarding processes which improved client engagement by 55%.
- Built deep relationships with clients to understand their specific needs and brought in \$1M in upsells to satisfy those needs.
- Successfully managed to convert \$1M worth of business from competitors who were introduced to me through existing client referrals.

Sales Representative

Don-Stroy Invest | May 2014 - Jun 2015

- Actively prospect for and develop customers.
- Cultivate relationships within all customer target markets.
- Give presentations to all clients to educate them.

Junior corporate lawyer

GVSU | Oct 2013 - March 2014